<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cabrina Becker</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cabrina Becker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Language</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/10/new-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/10/new-language/</guid>
      <description>This is me and one of my best friends, Richa, who is also in this class, and we are working on the project together. I&#39;m going to use her in my example of how to use Python, since we learned it together.
 We learned assign values in values to variables, and then use those to run functions, such as multiplication.
trois = 3.0 cinq = 5 print(cinq*trois) ## 15.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Data Wrangling and Data Exploration Introduction These datasets were taken from the Association of American Medical Colleges (AAMC) website, and contain data from medical schools in 2019. &amp;quot;appsandmats&amp;quot; is a dataset that contains information about U.S. medical school applications and matriculants by school, state of legal residence, and sex, 2019-2020. &amp;quot;raceeth&amp;quot; contains information about the total enrollment by U.S. medical school and race/ethnicity for the 2019-2020 year. These are interesting to me because I am in the process of interviewing for medical schools in Texas only, and it is cool to see data from schools that I have interviewed for but also around the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Modeling, Testing, and Predicting Introduction I am going to be using the aSAH dataset, which summarizes several clinical and one laboratory variable of 113 patients with an aneurysmal subarachnoid hemorrhage The variables are defined as: NDKA:Nucleoside diphosphate kinase A wfn: World Federation of Neurological Surgeons, uses the Glasgow Coma Scale and presence of focal neurological deficits to grade the clinical severity of subarachnoid hemorrhage. grade 1: GCS 15, no motor deficit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
